Finding Aid for the Leo Smit Slide Collection, circa 1966-1991
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Miscellaneous, 1966-1989, VI.; Box 23-Box 29
  - Miscellaneous, 1967-1991, C.; Box 26-Box 29
    - Miscellaneous (4), 1969-1991, 631 slides (Box 29)
      Sunsets, 1991 (24 slides)
      Sunsets, 1987 (19 slides)
      Travel/sunsets, 1986 (33 slides)
      Letchworth, 1983 (15 slides)
      OK Cy [Oklahoma City?], 1988 (2 slides)
      Sea Bluff, 1986 (20 slides)
      Aspen, 1976 (23 slides)
      St. Louis Arch, 1977 (18 slides)
      Mt. McKinley, 1969 (15 slides)
      Monterey, 1971 (23 slides)
      Santa Fe Opera; Cochiti; Suzie Berio, 1970 (23 slides)
      Indian Museum, 1970 (20 slides)
      Emily Dickinson house, 1989 (28 slides)
      People, undated (15 slides)
      Colts versus Bills, 1971 (8 slides)
      Art, 1971 (6 slides)
      Jan/Phil, 1987 (20 slides)
      Unlabeled miscellaneous, undated (74 slides)
      Unlabeled miscellaneous, undated (48 slides)
- Additions, undated, VII.; Box 30-32
  Box 30 contains images of people. Images of people in Boxes 31-32 have been marked with post-it notes. Full description is lacking.
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
Musicians--Slides; Slides (Photography)--Private collections; Smit, Leo, 1921-1999--Slide collections
Genres
Slides
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
Leo Smit Score Collection, circa 1940-1998
Mus. Arc. 6.1
The collection consists of 104 scores by Leo Smit, principally in copies of holographs. There are also another 43 items arranged or transcribed by Smit, inscribed to or by Smit, scores marked for performance by Smit, and miscellaneous scores.
Leo Smit Papers, 1939-2000
Mus. Arc. 6.2
A small collection of personal documents, writings by Smit, correspondence (chiefly photocopies of letters from Aaron Copland to Smit), clippings, programs, and lecture materials.
Leo Smit Photograph Collection, circa 1926-1999
Mus. Arc. 6.3
Chiefly black and white photographs documenting Leo Smit's life and career in music.
Remembering Leo Smit (1921-1999)
An online exhibit commemorating the life and career of Leo Smit. It contains many images of Smit as well as photographs taken by him. A list of Smit's compositions, compiled by the composer, is also included.